

Professional Summary

Experienced chef with over seven years of kitchen experience. Develops unique recipes with knowledge in nutritional values for balanced meals, according to desired lifestyles and innovative seasonal menus with local ingredients. Proven culinary leader with strong workflow coordination, training and communication skills.

Skills

- Recipes and menu planning
- Sanitation guidelines
- Kitchen equipment operation and maintenance
- Signature Dish Creation
- Food Plating and Presentation
- Performance assessments
- Payroll and scheduling
- Workflow Optimization
- Forecasting and Planning
- Budgeting and Cost Control

- English
- Castellano
- Italian
- Portuguese

Tiago Borges

+34674880124



tiagodoborges@gmail.com

Professional Experience

since January 2023

Milagros Goa, India - Chef

Supporting and setting Milagros restaurant in Goa, India

since January 2022

Private Chef

Started dedicating my time to host friends, families, weddings and parties as a Private Chef. Collaboration with La Grande Bouffe, an amazing catering company from Santa Eulalia, Ibiza

March 2021 - January 2022

Bottega Il Buco - Chef

Going back to Bottega to save their quality food reputation.

June 2021 - December 2021

WOW IBIZA - Head Chef

Cooking worldwide food, using techniques from Michelin Star restaurants to soul food, offering very interesting flavour combinations.

March 2019 -January 2020

Bottega Il Buco - Chef

Keeping a line of Italian healthy food, where the best ingredients alongisde simplicity would please any guest.

September 2017 – August 2018

Juniper Hill - Sous Chef

Opening of my favourite restaurant in the world, alongside with Josh DeChellis, world class Chef.

August 2016 - July 2017

AZOR Hotel - Floater

First job after school, managing from pizza oven to hotel breakfasts, Josper, line cook, etc...

Educational Background

September 2013 - July 2016

Escola de Formação Turistica e Hoteleira

São Miguel, Azores